[{"answer": "Well, I think it was a sentiment of frustration this morning because we hadn't had -- seen a real response here in Staten Island, but you know, we had our senators out here today, and I can say that the Red Cross is on the grounds right now.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Do you endorse what he said?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "ALLIOTAKIS: Absolutely not.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Do people there feel comfortable that this is going ahead?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "He's doing good.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "First of all, how is he doing?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Right now, we all need help.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Compared to the events and the aftermath of 9/11, how do you view what is happening in Staten Island?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "So you did not see a woman with two children?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "He took a concrete flower pot.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "And what did he do?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "He didn't ask to come in.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Well, let me ask you, the man -- if a man threw a flower pot, did you let the man in your house?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "All right, so...", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "I couldn't -- what could I do to help him?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's really important, Piers, is whether I believed him or not, he did acknowledge that there was a man who came by, and the man threw something at his back door and he wasn't willing to help the man.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Did you believe him, I suppose, is the obvious question?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, our initial reaction was from the police who were on the scene.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "What is the reaction of the community there to what's happened there?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "You know, I'm going to spend time in the postmortem looking at pre-storm preparedness.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "And are you satisfied they're doing all they can to get people back to full power?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I've got half my staff, never mind anybody else in New York, all homeless, wondering when the hell they're getting their power back.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "How are you tonight?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes, no, it's an extraordinary ordeal that everyone is going through, and we're working very hard to get the power back on as quick as we can.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "What do you say to people who are now heading towards day four with no power and not able to be in their homes or to use water or anything?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, we're saying that we're going to get almost everybody, virtually everyone back by next weekend.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Can you give a guarantee that everybody will be back on a week by Saturday, for instance?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, shortly after 7:30 or 8:00, the power went out.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "We need to go now, yeah.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "You stayed there, I believe, until about 3:00 a.m. and then in rushed firemen and other emergency services saying, grab your baby and get out now?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "There was a hurricane raging outside?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "You were carried down nine floors?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "But it was scary because you were taken to the wrong hospital first, right?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "He is fine, yes.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "And he is fine?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I'm quite upset, actually.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "What do you feel about the fact that these back-up generators failed?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you know, the planet is warmer than it was and people have something to do with it.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "You are a firm believer in climate change being responsible for this?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "That we have a very limited data series on hurricanes.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "On that one point, what do you say?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "As consumer, I want that power back immediately.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Were you satisfied with his explanation?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I think that Con-Ed for right now is -- I think they are scrambling.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "So New Yorkers are impatient but do you think they are right to be angry now?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "121101pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Charles, we'll start with you?", "qSentId": 614}]